A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, Fellows Reports, SG 1, Series 20.2A FA428
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, Fellows Reports, SG 1, Series 20.2A
1918-1988
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund
FA428
6 Cubic Feet 12 document boxes and 1 photo box.
Arrangement
Reports are arranged alphabetically by the last name of the Fellow.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Other Finding Aids note
Other available finding aids describing the Commonwealth Fund records include:
FA247 Commonwealth Fund Harkness House drawings
FA276 Commonwealth Fund records, Annual Reports, SG 1, Series 4
FA277 Commonwealth Fund records, Archives/Library, SG 1, Series 5
FA278 Commonwealth Fund records, Austrian Program, SG 1, Series 6
FA279 Commonwealth Fund records, Board of Directors, SG 1, Series 7
FA280 Commonwealth Fund records, Capital Grants, SG 1, Series 8
FA281 Commonwealth Fund records, Child Health Demonstrations, SG 1, Series 9
FA282 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Community Clinics, SG 1, Series 10
FA283 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Health Studies, SG 1, Series 11
FA284 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Public Health, SG 1, Series 12
FA285 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13
FA286 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14
FA287 Commonwealth Fund records, Educational Research, SG 1, Series 15
FA288 Commonwealth Fund records, English Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 16
FA289 Commonwealth Fund records, Finance Committee, SG 1, Series 17
FA290 Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18
FA291 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Family, SG 1, Series 19
FA292 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20
FA428 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, Fellows Reports, SG 1, Series 20A
FA293 Commonwealth Fund records, Institute for Child Guidance, SG 1, Series 21
FA294 Commonwealth Fund records, Interface Program, SG 1, Series 22
FA295 Commonwealth Fund records, Legal Research Program, SG 1, Series 23
FA296 Commonwealth Fund records, Living at Home Program, SG 1, Series 24
FA297 Commonwealth Fund records, Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 25
FA298 Commonwealth Fund records, Miscellaneous - unprocessed
FA299 Commonwealth Fund records, Personnel - unprocessed
FA300 Commonwealth Fund records, Pilgrim Trust, SG 1, Series 28
FA301 Commonwealth Fund records, Program for the Prevention of Delinquency, SG 1, Series 29
FA302 Commonwealth Fund records, Reference Files, SG 1, Series 30
FA303 Commonwealth Fund records, Reports of the General Director, SG 1, Series 31
FA304 Commonwealth Fund records, Treasurer, SG 1, Series 32
FA305 Commonwealth Fund records, Turndown Lists, SG 1, Series 33 - unprocessed
FA306 Commonwealth Fund records, Vertical File (R. Fitz), SG 1, Series 34 - unprocessed
FA307 Commonwealth Fund records, Visual Materials, SG 1, Series 35
FA389 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1
FA390 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Officers Files, SG 1, Series 2
FA429 Commonwealth Fund records, President, Margaret E. Mahoney, SG 2, Series 1
FA430 Commonwealth Fund records, Book Program, SG 2, Series 2
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The Rockefeller Archive Center acquired a major portion of the Commonwealth Fund archives in 1986. This initial deposit included fifty-five cubic feet of administrative records and fellowship files from the Fund's Harkness Fellowship offices in New York and London. Subsequent transfers of records, primarily fellowship files, added another seventy cubic feet of documents.
Biographical/Historical note
The Commonwealth Fund was established in 1918 with an endowment of $10 million from Mrs. Stephen V. Harkness for "benevolent, religious, educational and like purposes." The early grants supported a variety of programs while generally promoting welfare, especially child welfare. Several grants were made in the field of medical research, but the Board of Directors decided in 1920 that this field was already sufficiently supported by other philanthropic organizations.
Despite this decision, by the mid-1920s the chief interest of the Fund had become public health, including mental hygiene, community health, rural hospitals, medical research, and medical education. Other grant areas included war relief, educational and legal research, child welfare, and international medical fellowships.
Biographical/Historical note
The Harkness Fellowship program followed the philanthropic aims of Edward S. Harkness, his mother Anna M. Harkness, and his wife Mary. When the Commonwealth Fund was established in 1918 in New York, its mandate was simply "to do something for the welfare of mankind." Edward Harkness' fondness for the British people and his desire to promote closer relationships between the U.S. and Great Britain stemmed from his personal love of England's traditions, particularly the treasures of the independent colleges at Oxford and Cambridge. The fellowship program began in 1925 with twenty fellowships for British graduate students to study in the United States. According to the Fund's annual report for that year, the program stemmed from the trustees' belief that "International understanding can be provided in no more practicable way than through the provision of International opportunities for education and travel to young men and women of outstanding character and ability." By helping potential British leaders become "familiar... with the institutions, customs, and ways of thinking" in the U.S., the program would create "a force for mutual understanding and good feeling" which would in turn promote "unity of thought and purpose on the part of the two great English speaking nations of the world."
Over the years, a number of changes in the original guidelines of the program broadened the scope of the fellowships. In 1929, the program also provided civil service fellowships to British subjects holding posts in various overseas departments of the British government. This broadened eligibility to include candidates from government service in Australia and New Zealand.
Eligibility was expanded again in 1959 to include non-civil servants in New Zealand and Australia, and eventually in 1960, applicants from Italy, France, Holland, Germany, Switzerland, and Norway were also considered.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IX; IV 4B 4
Scope and Contents note
The records of the Harkness Fellowships reflect the close personal relationship the Fund Instituted with over 1,800 fellows.
The program guidelines required that every fellow spend a significant portion of the fellowship in travel, an "obligation" highly prized by the fellows. Their travel experiences were an important educational factor and lasting benefit, and were often praised in the reports the fellows were required to submit after their return home.
These fellowship reports, written from the viewpoint of a foreigner, provide tremendous insight into American culture. Indeed, one Harkness fellow based a career on such insights. "It changed my life," Alistair Cooke wrote of his fellowship in literature shortly after completing it in 1932.
Education, Rural; Hygiene; Medical research; War relief; Child welfare; Medicine -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Medicine, Rural; Public welfare; Child psychology; Legal issues; Law; Child mental health; Legal research; Mental health; United States; New York (State); Public health; Medical education; New York (N.Y.)
- Fellows Reports, 1918-1988; 20.2A; 6 Cubic Feet 12 document boxes.
  - Abraham, Michael F., 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abravanel, Daniela, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Acton, Peter Hampden, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen, Paul Howard, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alman, John H., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alonso, Kirsten Baier, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Anderson, Hilary, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Appels, Rudolph, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Austin, Peter, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Baily, John, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bannard, Edward Yorke, 1956-1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Barclay, William A., 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Barker, Simon R., 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Barton, Nicholas James, 1967-1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Baskerville, Stephen, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bathurst, James C., 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Baumfield, D. L., 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Baumgart, I. L., 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Beam, Charles R., 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Beauman, Christopher, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bellamy, Alec, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 21-22)
  - Bernal, Martin, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Besana, Mario, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Binns, Kenneth, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Blackman, David J., 1968-1973 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Boden, Margaret, 1962-1967 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Boettcher, Barry, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Bolognesi, Martino, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Boshier, John F., 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Bonarius, Joannes, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Bookbinder, Alan, 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Bottelier, Pieter, 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Boyle, James A., 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Brambilla, Roberto G., 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Brown, Arthur, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Brown, Lesley C., 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Brumm, Ursula, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Brunskill, R. W., 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Burns, Sandra P., 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Calthrop, Paul, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Cameron, Robert L., 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Campbell, Alastair V., 1962-1964 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Campbell, Andrew, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Carstairs, Andrew D., 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Caulcott, Thomas H., 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Cavalli, Alesandro, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Cavander, Kenneth, 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Chaloner, William G., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Chandler, Geoffrey, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Chrimes, Neil Roy, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Clyne, Henry H., 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Collings, T. W. R., 1963-1965 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Cornford, James P., 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Corpet, Francois, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Cox, C. Barry, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Craske, Peter, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Crease, Susan E., 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Crichton, Richard, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Culpin, Robert, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Cumpsty, J. S., 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Curnow, R. N., 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Davies, Howard, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Davies, Louis W., 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Defay - Flausch, Marianne, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - DeGraeve, M. Christine, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Delafons, John, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 67-69)
  - Derrington, Patrice A., 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Deschamps, Robert, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Deverall, Brian J., 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Dobson, Mary J., 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Donati, Ada, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Doornbos, Martin, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Dorel, Martine A., 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Duffy, Francis, 1966-1974 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Duffy, Simon P., 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Dunsby, Jonathan, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Dunsire, Andy, 1951-1952 (Box 3, Folder 80-81)
  - Dupre, John, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Dwyer, Terrance, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Elvin, Mark, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Ernotte, Andre, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Evans, Hywel W., 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Evans, Philips B., 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Fane, Charles George, 1968-1972 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Farrell, James G., 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Feick, Jurgen, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Fells, Peter, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Folger, Michael Thomas, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Foster, Shirley, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Frank, Armin Paul, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Gabler, Hans Walter, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Gascoigne, Bamber, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Gelpi, Ettore, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Gevers, Michel, 1969-1975 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Gibson, Norman J., 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - Glass David S., 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Goldman, Lawrence, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Gombrich, Richard F., 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Goodhart, William H., 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Gosling, David, 1957-1959 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Graham, Leslie, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Gray, Roger Michael, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Greenman, Jonathan, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Gresford, Guy B., 1957 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Gridley, Richard, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Gruenberg, Karl, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Gullvag, Ingemund, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Hallan, Anthony, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Halliday, John S., 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Handy, Nicholas C., 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Hart, Stuart B., 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Hatherton, Trevor, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Harvey, Jonathan, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Hayhoe, Thomas, 1978-1980 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Heinz, Walter R., 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Hemingway, John, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Henry, Jean Pierre, 1971-1974 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Herding, Richard, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Herman, David, 1979-1981 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Hinde, Leonard T., 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Hofmann, Michael, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Hogarth, Robin M., 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Hollein, Hans, 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Hollis, Martin, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Hope, Francis, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Horwitz, Christopher M., 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 130)
  - Houlton, Robert, 1965-1967 (Box 5, Folder 131)
  - Hunter, John G., 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 132)
  - Iest, Karin, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 133)
  - Ions, Edmund, 1958-1960 (Box 5, Folder 134)
  - Iverach, David, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 135)
  - Jackson, Charles V., 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 136)
  - Jackson, Desmond S., 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 137)
  - James, Kenneth C. W., 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 138)
  - Janson, Philippe A., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 139)
  - Janssens, Gerard, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Jennings, Wendy (Stallworthy), 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Jewell, Nicholas P., 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Jinks, John L., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - Johnson, Clifford, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 144)
  - Johnston, Judith A., 1978-1979 (Box 5, Folder 145)
  - Jones, Alexandra, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 146)
  - Jones, Derek, 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Jupp, Allen H., 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Kellan, Hugh, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Kendall, Bridget, 1978-1980 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Kibble, Thomas W. B., 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Kirk-Greene, Anthony, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Kirkland, Andrew, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Kitching, John, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Klabbers, Jan H. G., 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Kogan, M., 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Kroes, Robert, 1950- (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Kupers, Frits, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Laird, Sally, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Lambert, Daniel, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Lane, J. C., 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Law, Harry Davis, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - Ledderose, Lothar, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Leech, Geoffrey, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 164)
  - Leenhouts, Anneke, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 165)
  - Leggat, George, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 166)
  - Leibbrandt, Gottfried J., 1961-1963 (Box 6, Folder 167)
  - Lenaerts, Koenraad Maria Jan Suzanna, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 168)
  - Lester, A. P., 1960-1962 (Box 6, Folder 169)
  - Lodge, David, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 170)
  - Logan, Walter E. M, 1950-1951 (Box 6, Folder 171)
  - Lojacono, Gian Maria, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 172)
  - Long, Anthony Roger, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 173)
  - Lough, Roger M., 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 174)
  - Lynden- Bell, Donald, 1960-1962 (Box 6, Folder 175)
  - Macindoe, S. L., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 176)
  - Mackenzie, Ian William, 1977-1979 (Box 6, Folder 177)
  - Manning, Susan L., 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 178)
  - Mansfield, Jonathan, 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 179)
  - Marchini-Camia, Antonio, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 180)
  - Mariti, Paolo, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 181)
  - Marsh, Roger, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 182)
  - Martinotti, Guido, 1962-1964 (Box 6, Folder 183)
  - Masnata, Frangois, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Maughan, Deryck G., 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - Mayer, Colin P., 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Mayne, Edward A., 1951-1952 (Box 6, Folder 187-188)
  - McCombie, Charles W., 1955-1957 (Box 7, Folder 189)
  - McCutheon, Stuart N., 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 190)
  - McDougall, Ian Ross, 1972-1974 (Box 7, Folder 191)
  - McGregor, Craig, undated (Box 7, Folder 192)
  - McIntosh, J. L, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 193)
  - McKerrell, Archie, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 194)
  - McKillop, James H., 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 195)
  - McKinnon, Ken R., 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 196)
  - McLachlan, Andrew David, 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 197-198)
    - 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 198)
  - McMullen, David L., 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 199)
  - McNatty, Kenneth P., 1977-1979 (Box 7, Folder 200)
  - McNicol, George P., 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 201)
  - Mears, Dennison P, 1953-1955 (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - Medd, David L. / Crowley, Mary, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 203)
  - Mees, Alistair I., 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 204)
  - Milgate, Rodney A., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 205)
  - Mills, Stephen, 1978-1980 (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - Montgomerie, James F., 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 207)
  - Moody, Keith G., 1951-1953 (Box 7, Folder 208)
  - Moore, Gerald K. F., 1963-1965 (Box 7, Folder 209)
  - Moores, Brian, undated (Box 7, Folder 210)
  - Moreton, N. Edwina, 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 211)
  - Morgan, Michael James, 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 212)
  - Morgan, Rosemary, 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - Morris, G. Eryl, 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 214)
  - Mortimer, Barry, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 215)
  - Morton, James, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 216)
  - Morton, Stewart F., 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 217)
  - Moscati,Roberto, 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 218)
  - Moss, Donald, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - Mountfield, Peter, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 220)
  - Murphy, C. H. W., 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 221-222)
  - Murray, C. H. de Coligny, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 223)
  - Nairac, J. L., 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 224)
  - Nyssen, Ute, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 225)
  - O'Driscoll, E. S., 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 226)
  - Oliver, Alexander, 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 227)
  - O'Riordan, Timothy, 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 228)
  - Osborne, Donald V., 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 229)
  - Osgood, Stephen, 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 230)
  - Paci, Massimo, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 231)
  - Parsons, William T., 1959-1969 (Box 8, Folder 232)
  - Part, Anthony, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 233)
  - Payne, W. J. A., 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 234)
  - Pearson, John, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 235)
  - Pearson, Lucia, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Folder 236)
  - Peel, Richard J., 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 237)
  - Penfold, Anthony, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 238)
  - Pepper Davis, Christine, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 239)
  - Peppiat, Hugh S. K., 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 240)
  - Peskine, Alan, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 241)
  - Peterson, A. W., 1956 (Box 8, Folder 242)
  - Petti, Anthony G., 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 243)
  - Phillips, Leon F., 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 244)
  - Pickles, Alan T., 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 245)
  - Pilling, Joseph G., 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 246)
  - Pitteway, Michael, 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 247)
  - Plowden, William, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 248)
  - Pocock, Edward R., 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 249)
  - Pode, John S. F., 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 250)
  - Powell, Edward, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 251)
  - Power, Desmond John, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 252)
  - Puketapu, Ihakara, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 253)
  - Quin, Ann, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 254)
  - Rainbird, Alan, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 255)
  - Rattray, Peter V., 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 256)
  - Read, Piers Paul, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 257)
  - Reed, Colin B. M., 1963-1965 (Box 9, Folder 258)
  - Rees, Neville, T., 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 259)
  - Reid, Kenneth J., 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 260)
  - Rempoulis, Andrew M., 1962-1964 (Box 9, Folder 261)
  - Renaud, Philippe, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 262)
  - Rhodes, Douglas N., 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 263)
  - Rice, Anthony L., 1962-1964 (Box 9, Folder 264)
  - Ridley, J. W., 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 265)
  - Roberts, John, 1967-1969 (Box 9, Folder 266)
  - Roberts, Lewis E. J., 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 267)
  - Roope, Clover, 1964-1966 (Box 9, Folder 268)
  - Rosamund, John, 1976-1978 (Box 9, Folder 269)
  - Rossi-Crespi, Giulio, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 270)
  - Rowe, Henry P., undated (Box 9, Folder 271)
  - Rowe, Richard D., 1964-1966 (Box 9, Folder 272)
  - Rowland, Christopher, undated (Box 9, Folder 273)
  - Runcie, John, 1962-1964 (Box 9, Folder 274)
  - Russell, Keith R, 1978-1980 (Box 9, Folder 275)
  - Rutherford, Andrew F., 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 276)
  - Sandercock, Edward R., 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 277)
  - Sanders, Neil, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 278)
  - Sanderson, Christopher, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 279)
  - Sargent, Kenneth, 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 280)
  - Scherer, Franz, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 281)
  - Schmodde, Helge Jan, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 282)
  - Sclater, J. R., 1962-1964 (Box 10, Folder 283)
  - Scott, Malcolm, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 284)
  - Scrymgour, Peter, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 285)
  - Severin, Giles Timothy, 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 286)
  - Shapcott, Joanne, 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 287)
  - Shears, Lawrence William, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 288)
  - Sherwood, P. Louis, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 289)
  - Singh, Rabinder, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 290)
  - Sixsmith, Martin, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 291)
  - Smith, David C., 1959-1960 (Box 10, Folder 292)
  - Smith, Edward Kinsey Morgan, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 293)
  - Smith, Philip, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 294)
  - Snare, Austin, 1960-1961 (Box 10, Folder 295)
  - Sole, Christopher J., 1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 296)
  - Standage, Simon, undated (Box 10, Folder 297)
  - Steeds, David, undated (Box 10, Folder 298)
  - Steele, Jonathan, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 299)
  - Stephens, Nicholas, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 300)
  - Stevens, Jack, undated (Box 10, Folder 301)
  - Strain, Alastair, 1978-1980 (Box 10, Folder 302)
  - Strittmatter, P. A., 1964-1966 (Box 10, Folder 303)
  - Sugar, Peter C., 1958-1960 (Box 10, Folder 304)
  - Swaab, Peter A., 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 305)
  - Sweetman, Donald R., 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 306)
  - Sykes, Richard D., 1957-1959 (Box 10, Folder 307)
  - Tait, Malcolm, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 308)
  - Talbot, Jim, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 309)
  - Tanner, Paul A., 1958-1960 (Box 10, Folder 310)
  - Tayler, Roger J., 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 311)